mahobeachcam.com 2019-05-03

# PTZtv - Privacy Policy

**What information do we collect?**

You may visit our free-to-view sites anonymously and are not required to register or sign-in. If you choose to register for our PTZtv Premium service, you will be required to provide an email address.

If you choose to fill out and submit a contact or "wave request" form, you may be asked to enter your name, e-mail address or phone number.  

Like most websites, our servers automatically record the page requests made when you visit our sites. These “server logs” typically include your web request, IP address, browser type, browser language and the date/time of your access. These logs are only used internally for debugging technical issues or tracing connection problems. Typically, they are auto-deleted after 7-30 days, depending on server application. In extrememly rare circumstances, logs may be preserved for longer periods when access is requested under subpoena from a law enforcement agency. PTZtv cooperates fully with all legitimate law enforcement inquiries.  

Our PTZtv Premium and PTZtv Gallery websites can involve eCommerce transactions if you choose to purchase from them. Those transactions necessitate the sharing of more personal information, including credit card numbers if that payment method is selected.  

PTZtv Premium transactions are handled by Tinypass/Piano and their privacy policy is [here](https://piano.io/privacy/).

PTZtv Gallery transactions are handled by SmugMug, Inc. and their privacy policy is [here](https://www.smugmug.com/about/privacy).  

**How do we use your information?**

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

  * To improve our website. We continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you.
  * To improve customer service. Your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs.
  * To send periodic emails.
  * To protect our sites and our business from malicious or tortious interference and copyright theft.

The email address you provide may be used to send you information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions.

We use your IP address to perform IP geolocation at the country level but do not save or retain this geo data unless access is attempted from a prohibited region. We may also offer different services or no service at all depending on your geolocated origin.

**How do our partners use your information?**

We contract with Google for both advertising and site traffic analytics. How they use the information they collect and how you can control it are explained [here](https://www.google.com/policies/technologies/partner-sites/).

Google Analytics privacy policy is [here](https://www.google.com/analytics/learn/privacy.html). They compile aggregate, non-personal data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and features in the future. They are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business. Data they collect is deleted after 26 months.

We also contract with Sovrn for advertising. How they use information and how you can opt-out are explained [here](https://www.sovrn.com/privacy-policy/).

Our websites also display advertising from DistrictM and their privacy policy is [here](https://districtm.net/en/page/platforms-data-and-privacy-policy/).

On the Roku platform and for the PTZtv Roku channel, we are represented exclusively by [BaronsMedia.com](http://www.baronsmedia.com/) and their privacy policy is [here](http://baronsmedia.com/privacy-policy/).

Users may also opt out of the use of cookies for interest-based advertising by visiting [aboutads.info](http://optout.aboutads.info/) .

Our advertising partners may source ads from networks that are [members](http://www.networkadvertising.org/participating-networks/) of the Network Advertising Initiative (NAI) and their opt-out page for interest-based advertising is [here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp). 

We also include social media plug-ins from both Facebook and Twitter. Their policies for information collection and use are explained at the following links :

We include maps from Marine Traffic and Flightradar24 that can include advertising unless removed by separate subscription with the respective supplier. For more information, please consult the Marine Traffic privacy policy [here](https://www.marinetraffic.com/en/p/privacy-policy) and Flightradar24 privacy policy [here](https://www.flightradar24.com/privacy-policy).

We include free clocks from timeanddate.com and their privacy policy is [here](https://www.timeanddate.com/clocks/privacy.html).

We include weather widgets from DarkSky and their privacy policy is [here](https://darksky.net/privacy).

Tinypass/Piano manage our paid content access service known as PTZtv Premium and collect personally identifiable information in order to facilitate payments, manage subscriptions and grant site access. Their privacy policy is linked above.

**What are cookies?  
 **

Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfer to your computer's hard drive through your web browser (if you allow) that enable the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.

PTZtv makes minimal use of cookies for the sole purpose of saving and restoring viewer preferences, options and consent.

Third party vendors -- including Google, Sovrn and other partners listed above -- use cookies on our sites. Cookies enable some of these vendors to serve ads to our users based on their visits to our sites and/or other sites on the Internet. Personalized ads are more effective and help us maintain a free-to-view strategy.

**Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

**Email Policy**

We comply with the federal CAN-SPAM Act. You can always opt out of receipt of further email correspondence from us or our affiliates. We will not sell, rent, or trade your email address to any unaffiliated third-party without your permission except in the sale or transfer of our business.

**Third party links**

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our websites. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

**California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.

**Online Privacy Policy Only**

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our websites and not to information collected offline.

**Terms and Conditions**

Please also visit our [Terms and Conditions](https://www.ptztv.com/about-us/terms-conditions/) section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our websites.

**Your Consent**

By using our websites, you consent to our privacy policy.

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will update the Privacy Policy modification date below.

This policy was last modified on **February 11th, 2019**

If you have further questions, please contact us by email to [info@ptztv.com](mailto:info@ptztv.com)
